popplet.com 2014-04-11

# Popplet - Privacy Policy

**Popplet Privacy Policy**

**Our Commitment to Privacy.** At Notion Inc. ( **"Popplet," "we,"** or **"us"** ), we respect the privacy of your information and have provided this explanation about our online information practices to show our commitment to protecting your privacy. By using Popplet site at URL: [_http://www.popplet.com_](http://www.popplet.com/) / (the **"Site"** ) or the services provided through the Site (the **"Services"** ), we may collect information about you, and use and disclose such information, as described in this privacy policy ( **"Privacy Policy"** ). This Privacy Policy describes Popplet's collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information and Anonymous Information (each as defined below) of both Visitors and Registered Users (as defined in our General Terms and Conditions of Use located at [**_www.popplet.com/terms_**](http://www.popplet.com/terms) ). **"Personal Information"** means your contact information (e.g., your name, address, email address, or telephone number) and any other non-public information that is associated with your contact information. **"Anonymous Information"** means information that is not linked to Personal Information and does not enable contact with any identifiable person.

THE SITE AND SERVICES ARE HOSTED IN THE UNITED STATES. IF YOU ARE A USER ACCESSING THE SITE OR SERVICES FROM THE EUROPEAN UNION, ASIA, OR ANY OTHER REGION WITH LAWS OR REGULATIONS GOVERNING PERSONAL DATA COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE THAT DIFFER FROM UNITED STATES LAWS, PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT THROUGH YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SITE OR SERVICES, WHICH IS GOVERNED BY UNITED STATES LAW, THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND OUR TERMS OF SERVICE, YOU ARE TRANSFERRING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE UNITED STATES AND YOU CONSENT TO THAT TRANSFER. ADDITIONALLY, YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE PROCESSED IN COUNTRIES (INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES) WHERE LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN IN YOUR COUNTRY.

**The Information We Collect.** We collect Personal Information and Anonymous Information about you.

_Personal Information_ We collect Personal Information when you knowingly provide it to us. In order to use, access, or receive certain Services, you may be required to complete the applicable registration form accessible on the Site. For example, to become a Registered User you must provide your first and last name and email address. In addition, we collect Personal Information when you provide it through your creation of Popplet boards or your participation in discussion forums, surveys and/or sweepstakes, or when you correspond with us.

In addition, our Registered Users can invite other users to use the Services by entering their name and email address. It is possible that we may get your name and email address from one of our Registered Users.

_Anonymous Information Collected Via Technology._ As you use the Site or Services, certain Anonymous Information may also be passively collected and stored, such as your Internet protocol address, browser type, and access times. We may also use Cookies (as defined below) and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URLs) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed. **"Cookies"** are small pieces of information that a website sends to your browser while you are viewing a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your browser until you delete them) to improve your experience on the Site (e.g., by keeping you logged in). Persistent Cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, you may be logged out of certain portions of the Site .

**The Ways We Use Information.** We use Personal Information that you submit to us to administer your account, control access to the Site and Services, communicate with you, respond to your requests, provide Services, improve the quality of the Site and Services, facilitate invitations to use the Services and provide you with other information that may be useful or interesting to you. Such information may include regular newsletters and marketing emails, including contest entries and surveys. You can opt out of receiving newsletters from the Site by clicking the **"Unsubscribe"** link at the bottom of each email. Please note that even if you unsubscribe or opt-out, we may still send you Site and Service related emails.

We may also use your Personal Information to create Anonymous Information records by excluding information (such as your name or email address) that makes the information personally identifiable to you. We may use these records, and other Anonymous Information, to analyze usage patterns so that we may enhance the Site or Services.

**The Ways We Disclose Information.** We may disclose Personal Information

To third party vendors who help us make the Site or Services available, but only if they are contractually obligated to use the information in compliance with this Privacy Policy;

To third parties to whom you ask us to send Personal Information, including those to whom you send an invitation;

To any parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (collectively, **"Affiliates"** ), in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy

To a company that merges with, acquires, or purchases the assets of, Popplet, in which case such company may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy; or

If we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) resolve disputes, investigate problems, or enforce our terms of use; (b) comply with relevant laws or to respond to requests from law enforcement or other government officials relating to investigations or alleged illegal activity; or (c) protect and defend the rights or property of Popplet, you, or third-parties, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose Personal Information without subpoenas or warrants served on us.

We may disclose Anonymous Information to:

Third party vendors who may help us enhance or provide the Site or Services; or

To third parties to whom you ask us to send Personal Information.

In addition, any information which you post to a Popplet board (unless contained in a private Popplet Board that you have not shared with anyone), or to our discussion forums or otherwise choose to make publicly available, including your Personal Information, may be disclosed and available to all users who have access to that portion of the Site or Services, and is therefore no longer private. By using these our Services, you agree that we are not responsible for any such information that you disclose or communicate, and any disclosures you make are at your own risk.

**How You Can Update, Correct or Delete Your Information.**

_Updating and Correcting._ You may update your display name or password by emailing us at [_support@popplet.com_](mailto:support@popplet.com) from your email address on record or, if you are a Registered User, by editing your profile. Subsequent uses or disclosures of information by us will reflect those changes, but we have no ability to update any information previously disclosed to any third-party. Your Personal Information is necessary in order for us to send you newsletters or provide you access to the Services; therefore, if you delete such necessary information we may not be able to provide you certain Services.

_Deleting._ If you wish to have your Personal Information removed from our databases, you may contact us at [_support@popplet.com_](mailto:support@popplet.com) from your email address on record and let us know what Personal Information you want deleted. You may request deletion of your Personal Information by us, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete Personal Information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives.

**Children Under 13.** Protecting the privacy of all users is very important to us. We do not collect or maintain Personal Information from people we actually know are under 13 years old, and no part of the Site or Services is designed to attract people under 13 years old.

**Third Party Practices.** The Site or Services may contain links to other websites, including those of our partners. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. The privacy policy of a partner listed on our Site may differ from ours. We encourage you to read the privacy policy for each third-party website you visit before responding to any offers.

**Changes to Our Policy.** This Privacy Policy is subject to revision from time to time. We will post any revised version of the Privacy Policy on this Site. If we make any material changes to it, we will also send you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us (if any). Any amended Privacy Policy will be effective as of the date stated in the revised policy.

Any changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use or disclosure of Personal Information collected prior to the changes. If you do not agree to any of the changes, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to have us delete your Personal Information. Continued use of our Services following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the revised terms and conditions.

**Contact Us.** If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [_support@popplet.com_](mailto:support@popplet.com).
